ecocoins.io 2017-05-17

# EcoCoins.io

### Privacy Policy

## Scope

This Privacy Policy belongs to ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED (hereinafter referred to as the company, we, our). This Privacy Policy refers to information we receive from users of our resource https://www.ecocoins.com, our online services, recipients of our letters, as well as Internet users interacting with us in any way. It describes personal data we collect, the way we use, store and protect them.

### Collecting and Using Data

            **Voluntarily providing us your personal data, you as the User agree to their use by us according to this Privacy Policy. Providing us your personal data, you agree that such data may be transferred from your current location to locations of offices and servers of ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED, as well as third parties authorized within this Privacy Policy. Besides, providing us your personal data, you recognize and agree that such data may be transferred in cases stipulated by international legislation on the ground of corresponding requests to competence authorities and law enforcement agencies of the country of jurisdiction according to the citizenship of the User or a suffered party.**

####  **Data You Provide To Us**

 **            ** We collect information you provide us, including:  

  * your name, email, cell phone number, taxpayer identification number (e.g., US social insurance number) or other identification number issued by a public authority, date of birth, home address, IP-address when creating an account, forming your portfolio and sending a request for support;
  * email and phone numbers of your acquaintances if you decide to invite them to use ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED within our partner program when creating an account; while allowing your acquaintances to refuse from commercial messages they receive from us;
  * information on transactions you performed using our services, including scope of funds related to Bitcoin transactions, type of a transaction being performed and other related information.

####  **Other Data Collected**

 **           **  We can also automatically collect the following data:  

  * Cookies

            We use Cookies on our resource to collect data on your authorization and allowing you to move from one page to other one without the need of repeated entering our system to calculate visits and see which areas and features of our resources are popular. We do not combine information saved with Cookies with any other information you provide to us when staying on our resource. We can also use data collected using Cookies to adapt advertisement for you and trace popularity of our website. Use of Cookies and other technology allows us and third parties to collect information on your preferences in the Web-space during a certain period of time after we use our services.          

  * Analytics

            When you visit our website, we use indirect tools of analysis to collect data on your computer and Internet connection. This information includes IP-address of your computer and/or Internet provider at the time of accessing our web-resource; Internet-address of websites, where you place our link or from which you pass to our website before visiting our website; browser you use, as well as your actions and preferences on our website. All this information is used for internal purposes and understanding of the way in which our website is used, including for the purposes of improving our services.  

  * Site Management

            We collect data on using our website for administration, protection and improvement of internal services and our system, as well as to better understand preferences of visitors of our website and optimize content we serve; to learn problems of the server; to make summary statistics on the use of our resource, as well as to improve our marketing and studies.          

  * Do Not Track Command

            Our resource does not response currently to the “Do Not Track” command and operates as described in this Private Policy, without acceptance of similar commands. If we change our Policy in these terms in the future, we will give a detailed description in this Privacy Policy with a reference to the date of updating the Policy. **          
**

### **Protection of Data We Collect**

####  ****

 **            ** We use reasonable physical, electronic and procedural warranties to protect your personal data against loss, incorrect use, unauthorized access, distortion or destruction. Please pay attention that we are not liable for security of any data transferred to you through Internet channels, as well as any data you save, place or provide directly on the website of a third party defining its own security and privacy policy at its own discretion. Please pay attention that no way of transferring data through Internet channels or electronic storage is 100% safe. If you have additional questions concerning security, you can contact us. ****

### ****

### **Retention of Data We Collect** ****  
 ****

 **             I**f you wish to completely delete your ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED account, please contact us from your registered email. We may save information on you in our databases till your account is active or if necessary to subsequently provide you services pursuant to the current legislation.  
            We will save and use your personal data, if necessary, to perform our legal obligations, resolve disputes, as well as comply with the terms and conditions of signed agreements. Term of storage may exceed the period of our mutual relations, but it goes on till it is necessary for us to have sufficient data to answer any questions that may arise in the future. For example, we may need certain information we must save to prevent fraud, as well as for own legal protection and prevent or mitigate any damage we may suffer. Such saving is also possible if we reasonably believe that it is required by a law, other regulatory act, requirement or guiding principle. **** ****  
 ****

###  **Access to Information We Collect**

 **             **We will answer your request on accessing your personal information we collected within terms stipulated by the current legislation.  
            We are also ready for cooperation and provision of data to public authorities and law enforcement agencies of the country of jurisdiction according to the citizenship of the User or a suffered party on the ground of corresponding requests only in cases stipulated by international legislation.  
            In all other cases, provision of information to a third party is strictly prohibited by the Privacy Policy. ****  
 ****

###  **Sharing Data We Collect**

 **            ** We can transfer your information only in the following manner and on the following grounds: **  
**

  *  ****you have agreed to or otherwise authorized such transfer;
  * we have aggregated or anonymized information so that it does not allow your identification;
  * only in part related to third-party service providers we use in the provision of our services, including for certain advertisement, transactions or other financial and technological services (to hosting providers, email service providers in the verification of personal data, support, payment, etc.);
  * if it is stipulated or we believe that it is stipulated by the current legislation or within court proceedings;
  * for the purposes of protection of rights, property and security of ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED, our users and companies, including, for example, due to court proceedings, or to identify and prevent crime, fraud, restore and protect our intellectual rights;
  * due to sales, merger, transfer or reorganization of all or part of our business. ****  

 ****

###  **Email Communications**

 **             **If you enter our system to get information on our software products, updates and offers, we will use your name and email to send you such information. If you do not wish to get the above messages any more, you may refuse from subscription following instructions contained in the letters you receive or on our website. Please pay attention that we may send you messages with data on transactions, even if you unsubscribe from our marketing communications. Also, if your service is temporarily suspended for reasons of technical servicing, we may email you a corresponding notice. **  
**

###  **Links to Other Websites and Online Services**

 **             **Our website may contain links to other websites or Internet services, whose security or privacy policy may significantly differ from ours. If you provide your data to any of such websites or online services, such transfer of information is regulated by their security policy. We recommend you to read carefully Privacy Regulations of any website you visit. ******  
**

### **Changes to this Policy**  

###  ****

 **           **  We may change this Privacy Policy. If we make such changes, we notify you of this by specifying the date of changes in the upper part of the Policy. If we make significant changes, we will do it pursuant to the current regulatory requirements and will place a notice on our web-site warning you of significant changes before their entering into force. We also recommend you to review this page periodically to get the latest version of our Privacy Policy. **  
**

* * *

 **            ** To save your personal data accurate, complete and updated, please contact us through the “Contacts” section. We will take reasonable measures to update or change personal data you provided to us previously using our services available to us. Please do not hesitate to contact us in case of any questions on our Privacy Policy or informational practice of ECOMINING & CRYPTOTRADERS LIMITED services.  
 ****
